<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <!-- Afghanistan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_af">It is best to make travel plans for the spring or fall, particularly from April to June or from September to October. Spring is a pleasant season especially across north Afghanistan as the desert and hills turn a lively green.</string>
    <!-- Åland Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ax">The best time to visit the Åland Islands is between late spring and early autumn when the days are long and the weather is fairly warm (16&#8211;18C). Midsummer is an exciting time to visit the archipelago - the sun never sets and festivals abound while July is particularly busy with music festivals.</string>
    <!-- Albania -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_al">The best time to visit Albania is between April - June, and September - October, when the weather is just right for a mountain or a beach holiday. July - August is the peak season for tourists, but the coastal summer heat will be scorching, so you won\'t be able to explore the entirety of the country in peace.</string>
    <!-- Algeria -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_dz">The best time to visit Algeria is in spring and autumn as our temperature and rainfall chart goes to prove and if you’re looking for things to do in Algeria, as well as what not to do, read on as we’ve got the lowdown – from history tours to French phrasebooks. Algeria travel tips are best learned from a fellow traveller or one of our friends in Algeria which is why we’ve included a few choice pearls of wisdom to help you experience Algeria in the best way possible.</string>
    <!-- American Samoa -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_as">Visitors wishing to avoid serious tropical storms should avoid American Samoa between the months of November and April. This is not only the wet season, but also the tropical cyclone season throughout the South Pacific.</string>
    <!-- Andorra -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ad">The best time to visit Andorra is between April - October, when the weather is warm and dry. The temperature is quite warm, and the skies are clear, making this the perfect season for outdoor activities.</string>
    <!-- Angola -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ao">The best time to visit Angola is from June to October, when the weather is mild and sunny, and there\'s little risk of rain or storms. Broadly speaking, Angola has two distinct seasons – rainy and dry.</string>
    <!-- Anguilla -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ai">The best time to visit Anguilla is between May and August, when you stand the best chance of getting a good package deal and also avoiding the worst of the hurricane season (which generally runs from June 1 to November 30).</string>
    <!-- Antarctica -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_aq">In January, temperatures at the Peninsula average 34 Fahrenheit. Penguins begin hatching and wildlife, especially penguin chicks, is most plentiful during this time of year. Mid-February and March: Late summer in Antarctica, February and early March, is the best time to spot whales.</string>
    <!-- Antigua and Barbuda" -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ag">The best time to visit Antigua is from May to November, the island\'s off-season. Rates are cheapest at this time, and although there is a slight threat of hurricanes, the weather rarely escapes 80 degrees. You\'ll encounter less rain between December and April, but rates are expensive and crowds are abundant.</string>
    <!-- Argentina -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ar">When to travel will very much depend on where you want to visit. We consider Argentina springtime (October to mid-December) and autumn (April to mid-June) to be the best times to visit Argentina, avoiding the tourist crowds and peak season prices.</string>
    <!-- Armenia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_am">If you\'re planning to visit Armenia, the best time to head to this country would be the beginning and ending months of summer – late May and early June or else late September and early October. This is the time when the heat is comparatively less and the weather is comfortable and idle for exploration.</string>
    <!-- Aruba -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_aw">The best time to visit Aruba is from April to August – a huge window of time when the island\'s high prices take a holiday. And since the island sits well outside the hurricane belt, there\'s very little threat of tropical storms at this time. January to March features pleasant weather, but the room prices can soar.</string>
    <!-- Australia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_au">Best Time of Year to Visit Australia. Australia is enormous, with a wide range of climates. The northern states are typically warm year-round, while the southern states have cooler winters. December to February is summer; March to May is autumn; June to August is winter; and September to November is spring.</string>
    <!-- Austria -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_at">The best time to visit Austria is during the shoulder months, in spring, between April – May, and in fall, between September – October. The weather is excellent for outdoor activities, and the crowd is sparser. The high tourist season between June – August sees excellent weather and sunny days.</string>
    <!-- Azerbaijan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_az">Similarly, the Caspian Sea keeps summer manageable, but it can hit 40°C. So for hiking and culture, the best time to visit Azerbaijan is April-June and Sep-Oct. The mountains turn into a wildflower frenzy when snows melt and, at the same time spring brings the biggest holiday: Novruz Bayrami, around third week March.</string>
    <!-- Bahamas -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bs">The best time to visit the Bahamas is from mid-December to mid-April, the country\'s peak season. Though temperatures here are great year-round (they rarely dip below 60 degrees), the islands fall within the hurricane belt, so hurricanes may be a factor between June 1 and Nov. 30 (the Atlantic hurricane season).</string>
    <!-- Bahrain -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bh">December to March. The temperature conditions remain very pleasant in the archipelago during these months. March to April. If you are a Formula 1 fan, then you should definitely plan your visit to Bahrain during the months of March and April.</string>
    <!-- Bangladesh -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bd">During monsoon season, southeastern Bangladesh can get flattened by 1,000mm of rain in July – that\'s as much as the UK\'s yearly rainfall. Dry season is from November to March, when it\'s warm and sunny.</string>
    <!-- Barbados -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bb">The best time to visit Barbados is between July and November. Though these months fall within the Caribbean\'s hurricane season, hurricanes rarely hit the island, and you could attend one of the lively Crop Over Festival activities if you vacation during this time of year.</string>
    <!-- Belarus -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_by">Belarus has a cool continental climate, with warm summer days typically in the mid 20°Cs, and winters dropping below freezing. The best time to go to Belarus is from mid May to mid September, when it\'s comfortably warm. June, July and August are peak months for temps as well as tourists.</string>
    <!-- Belgium -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_be">"In season" in Belgium means from mid-April to mid-October. The peak of the tourist season is July and August, when the weather is at its finest, but you\'ll find Belgium every bit as attractive during other months.</string>
    <!-- Belize -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bz">The best time to visit Belize is from late November to mid-April, during the country\'s dry season. Although this peak season draws thousands of tourists, dealing with crowds is an easy sacrifice to make for warm temperatures, clear skies and easy access to the country\'s top attractions.</string>
    <!-- Benin -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bj">The desert-like north experiences more extreme temperatures, with November to June searingly hot, and June to October wetter and cooler. The best time to visit Benin is from November to February; not only is it dry, but you\'ll be able to attend the annual Vodoun Festival in Ouidah in January.</string>
    <!-- Bermuda -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bm">The best time to visit Bermuda is either March or April when the temperate weather becomes pleasant for beach bathing, even if it\'s not quite warm enough for swimming yet. And the prices aren\'t as high as they are during the busiest season, from May to October.</string>
    <!-- Bhutan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bt">October to December is the ideal time to visit Bhutan as the air is clear and fresh with sunny skies. January and February are colder, but from then until April the climate remains dry and pleasant and in late spring the famous rhododendrons bloom spectacularly, flooding the valleys with colour.</string>
    <!-- Bolivia (Plurinational State of) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bo">In most opinions, May-Oct is the best time to visit Bolivia, as the dry weather brings sapphire skies and less travel disruption. This is the Bolivian winter, though, so the highlands will be cold – and well below freezing in the desert at night, particularly in June-July.</string>
    <!-- Bonaire, Sint Eustatius and Saba -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bq">The best time to visit Bonaire is from May to October when there are fewer crowds and bargain hotel rates. If you\'re planning a winter getaway, keep in mind that December through April comprises the island\'s peak season, when the 80-degree weather yields packed hotels and higher prices.</string>
    <!-- Bosnia and Herzegovina -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ba">For hiking, the best time to go to Bosnia-Herzegovina is May, June or September, as it is less hot, although it never maxes out the thermometer in the same way as neighbouring Croatia.</string>
    <!-- Botswana -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bw">The best time to visit them is from May to September, during the Dry season and winter, resulting in more moderate temperatures. In addition, the Okavango is flooded from June to October.</string>
    <!-- Bouvet Island -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bv">Bouvet Island is Norway’s’ dependent territory so many travelers that are ought to visit all countries of the world are considering necessary to visit it. But most of them are forced to confine their visit to sailing around the island for its shores aren’t suitable for landing. Many travelers haven’t even chance to see the island due to thick fogs and clouds. Temperature range on the island is rather narrow. Averages are hovering between 4 and -5 °C (39&#8211;23 °F). However most of time it is slightly below zero (32 °F). Each month have roughly 25 days of overcast and 20 days with precipitation and its annual amount is above 750 mm (29.5”). In addition there are strong western winds with 10 m/s (20 mph).</string>
    <!-- Brazil -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_br">The Pantanal region has a consistent temperature throughout the year. Most rain falls from December to March and the best time to see animals is during the dry season from April/ May to October. Temperatures rarely drop below 20°C, even in the dead of winter from June to July.</string>
    <!-- British Indian Ocean Territory -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_io">Tropical marine; hot, humid, moderated by trade winds. December through February is the monsoon season; June through September is the drier winter season with slightly cooler temperatures.</string>
    <!-- United States Minor Outlying Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_um">The months of July to September should be avoided since in that time hurricanes are a common thing there. You won’t be able to enjoy yourself or you may even not be able to reach the place. You can face a lot of problems if you go travelling at that time within these islands.</string>
    <!-- Virgin Islands (British) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_vg">The British Virgin Islands enjoy a tropical climate with temperature highs of 28–31°C and prevailing coastal winds. March, April, July and August are popular months to visit as they typically receive the least rainfall.</string>
    <!-- Virgin Islands (U.S.) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_vi">The best time to visit the U.S. Virgin Islands is April to June, when you can expect mild weather and very little rainfall. In the USVI\'s peak season, from December to March, the temperature ranges from the mid-70s to high 80s with breezy evenings.</string>
    <!-- Brunei Darussalam -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bn">The high season to travel in Brunei is between June - September, but the best time to visit Brunei is between January and May. This is when the weather is dry and warm, but not too hot. February and March are the driest months of the entire year.Mar 30, 2017</string>
    <!-- Bulgaria -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bg">The best time to visit Bulgaria is during the shoulder months from April – May, and September – October, as the weather will be pleasant, and the prices will be lower. The high season is summer, from June – August.</string>
    <!-- Burkina Faso -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bf">The rainy season is between June and October. The best time therefore for visiting Burkina Faso is when the climate is the most temperate, between November and February despite the inconvenience of the pervasive fine sand caused by the harmattan.</string>
    <!-- Burundi -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bi">The best time to go to Burundi is from June until September, in which you have a pleasant or warm temperature and barely till little rainfall.</string>
    <!-- Cambodia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_kh">Most travelers visit Cambodia from November to March. If you prefer to dodge the crowds and go when prices are lower, the best time to visit Cambodia is from May to early October. Cambodia is warm year-round with temperatures rarely dipping below 68°F (20°C), wherever you go. Seasons are broken into wet and dry season.</string>
    <!-- Cameroon -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cm">Head to Cameroon from November to February for cooler, drier weather – but watch out for the dusty Saharan harmattan wind. Tropical Cameroon spans the dense, lush forests in the south, to the far drier north, nudging up towards the Sahel.</string>
    <!-- Canada -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ca">Mid-May to late June is a great time to visit Canada! There are not a lot of tourists so prices are reasonable. The summer tourist season has officially begun, although the first two weeks of May are generally quiet (and many attractions are still closed).</string>
    <!-- Cabo Verde -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cv">The best time to visit Cape Verde is between November and June – at this time of year, you can make the most of the white-sand beaches the islands are known for. The temperatures sit around the mid-to-high twenties, and there\'s hardly any rain.</string>
    <!-- Cayman Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ky">The best time to visit the Cayman Islands is between March and June when the hotel rates drop. The islands are warm year-round with average highs holding steady in the 80s. January and February are the coolest months with average lows in the high 60s.</string>
    <!-- Central African Republic -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cf">The best time to visit Central African Republic is in the December to May dry season.</string>
    <!-- Chad -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_td">The dry months from Oct/Nov to March are the best time to visit Chad – the rains may liven up the arid landscape but they wreak havoc with the largely unpaved roads and travelling north is virtually impossible.</string>
    <!-- Chile -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cl">The best time to visit Chilean Patagonia is November to early March (summertime in the southern hemisphere). Although you\'ll compete with heavy crowds during this peak season, the weather is ideal for exploring Torres del Paine National Park and Tierra del Fuego.</string>
    <!-- China -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cn">Weather-wise, the best times to visit China are spring (April–May) and autumn (September–October), when most of the popular places have their most tourism-friendly weather. 2. Summer (June–August) is a good time to travel, except for the crowds and the heat.</string>
    <!-- Christmas Island -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cx">Best Time to visit Christmas Island is between May to November. This period is the dry season where visitors won\'t run the risk of rainfall. December to April. This period is Christmas Island\'s wet season, and also the best time to visit. The annual red crab migration takes place during this period.</string>
    <!-- Cocos (Keeling) Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cc">The ideal time to visit Christmas Island and the Cocos (Keeling) Islands is during the south-east wind season between April and November.</string>
    <!-- Colombia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_co">December to March is the peak tourist season in the country and the prices soar everywhere. In addition to being sunny and warm, this period receives the least amount of rainfall except for Amazon region, making it the dry season. April to June mark the advent of rainy seasons in few areas such as Bogota, Medellin and Cali. As Easter falls during this period, bookings must be made in advance before visiting any destination. July to September is the dry season in the Andes region and exploring the countryside, jungles and beaches during this season is a great experience. Southern Colombia receives showers daily, but they don\'t last long. The Amazon region remains wet throughout the year. October to November is the low season in the country, and great deals and discounts can be availed on accommodation. Most of the regions such as Andean and Caribbean receive heavy rainfall leaving the cities wet and their roads blocked. Bright sunshine follows the prolonged period of rains, and one\'s travel is not as hindered as it might be expected. The lowlands being close to the equator experience little variation in their climate.</string>
    <!-- Comoros -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_km">The Comoros\' tropical climate sees these islands basking in warm temperatures all year round, though come from April to November for the driest and balmiest conditions.</string>
    <!-- Congo -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cg">Weather is everything in knowing when to go to the Congo. An equatorial setting means the Congo’s temperatures – and humidity levels - are high more or less all year: the average daytime temperature is 24°C (75°F) with nights recording between 16°C (61°F) and 21°C (70°F). Annual rainfall ranges from 1100mm to 2000mm and the year is divided into four seasons: a long rainy season from October to December; a short dry season from January to February; a short rainy season from March to April; and a long dry season from May to September.The principal travel destination in the Republic of Congo is the Odzala National Park, which experiences around 1500mm of rain a year: avoid the wettest months by travelling to Odzala between May and the end of December.</string>
    <!-- Congo (Democratic Republic of the) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cd">The line of the equator runs straight through the Democratic Republic of Congo, meaning temperatures vary little throughout the year. The daily mean for the capital of Kinshasa in the east fluctuates less than 5°C annually, from a low of 22.5°C in July to 27°C in April.</string>
    <!-- Cook Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ck">Rain clouds usually hang around Rarotonga\'s mountain peaks, even during the dry season (June to Aug). In short, there is no bad time weather-wise to visit the Cook Islands, although the shoulder months of April, May, September, and October usually provide the best combination of sunshine and warmth.</string>
    <!-- Costa Rica -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cr">The best time to visit Costa Rica is from mid-December to April (the dry season). This peak tourist season boasts plenty of sunshine making it an ideal time for exploring rainforests and lounging on beaches. That said, the dry season is the most popular (and expensive) time to visit.</string>
    <!-- Croatia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_hr">If you are not tied to school holidays, the best time to visit Croatia is during the “shoulder-season” months of May and June and September and October. Then you can expect pleasant sunny days ideal for swimming in the sea and sunbathing, with all the tourist facilities up and running but no crowds.</string>
    <!-- Cuba -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cu">The best time to visit is from December to May, when you can expect dry, sunny days and plenty of blue skies. The wet season begins in June and, previously, visitors to Cuba would have avoided travel entirely between August and October, when there is also a risk of hurricanes.</string>
    <!-- Curaçao -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cw">The best time to visit Curaçao is from May to November, during the off-peak season. During these months, you\'ll find the lowest airfares and hotel rates, with rooms often priced up to 50 percent lower than they are in the high season (especially during summer).</string>
    <!-- Cyprus -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cy">The exceptionally mild winters, the warmest in the Mediterranean, attract visitors from far and wide but the majority fail to venture into the North. The best time to visit Cyprus is the spring which often arrives as early as Feb.</string>
    <!-- Czech Republic -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_cz">The best time to visit Czech Republic is during spring (mid-March to mid May) and fall (September – mid November). This is when the crowds are just right, and the weather is consistently pleasant. The high season in Czech Republic is from June to August.</string>
    <!-- Denmark -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_dk">The best time to visit Denmark is May-Aug when the days are at their longest, temperatures are mild and the countryside is in full bloom. Spring and autumn are best for birdwatching on the west coast, with migrant species passing through.</string>
    <!-- Djibouti -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_dj">The best time to visit Djibouti is between November to January when the weather is comparatively cooler as these are the winter months for Djibouti.</string>
    <!-- Dominica -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_dm">The best time to go to Dominica is when the clouds have emptied once and for all, the greenery is at its most well fed, and the sun is bursting through. This is generally between the months of February and April. May is also stunning but hot and humid, so be prepared to sweat it out. Or come when it’s quiet, and just bring good raingear. Dominica is divine, rain or shine.</string>
    <!-- Dominican Republic -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_do">Hurricane season June to December (impacting the east), but aside from storms it\'s beautiful. Temperatures don’t vary much (mountains an exception). Deeply discounted rooms and some properties in resort areas close in October. Short but strong rains in Santo Domingo (through October). March is dry in Samaná; April is ideal throughout the country (also breezy). May to June is partly cloudy or partly sunny; chance of afternoon showers. July to August and the week before Easter are also high season. Expect higher hotel prices and crowded beaches. Whale-watching runs from around mid-January to mid-March. Most water sports are prohibited the week before Easter.</string>
    <!-- Ecuador -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ec">On the coast, the dry season from late May and June to November is unpleasantly cool, muggy and overcast. So if you like lying on beaches, then the rainy season from December / January to April / May is surprisingly the best time to visit Ecuador.</string>
    <!-- Egypt -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_eg">The best time to visit Egypt is from October to April, when temperatures are at their most pleasant. However, December and January constitute peak tourist season, and iconic sights like the Pyramids of Giza, the Temples of Luxor, and Abu Simbel can get uncomfortably crowded.</string>
    <!-- El Salvador -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sv">El Salvador\'s dry season (known locally as verano, or summer) runs between November and April, with a rainy season (invierno or winter) between May and October. In the rainy season, coastal and central regions typically suffer afternoon storms sandwiched between pleasant weather.</string>
    <!-- Equatorial Guinea -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gq">It is best to visit in July and August, as these are the driest months, but if you plan to visit the mainland and island regions, then December to February is your best bet. As you travel south along the coast from Bata rainfall levels increase, with the Río Muni estuary by Gabon being the wettest area.</string>
    <!-- Eritrea -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_er">The best time to go to Eritrea is from January until March, June and September until December, in which you have a pleasant or warm temperature and barely till mediocre rainfall. The highest average temperature in Eritrea is 30° in june and the lowest is 22° in december.</string>
    <!-- Estonia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ee">The most clement weather is from May to September, and while it can get a little crazy in Tallinn and Pärnu (especially in July and August), it\'s still the best time to visit. Almost all festivals are scheduled for summer, with the biggest celebrations saved for midsummer\'s eve.</string>
    <!-- Ethiopia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_et">Generally the best time to visit is between October and June, when it is the dry season. Rains tend to stop in early October, meaning afterwards the highlands are lush and green – perfect for trekking amongst pretty wildflowers that have sprung up. Be sure to bring a sweater all year round due to Ethiopia\'s elevation.</string>
    <!-- Falkland Islands (Malvinas) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_fk">The best time to visit the Falklands is between October and April, although within this timeframe November to February is likely to be more agreeable weather-wise.</string>
    <!-- Faroe Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_fo">Even though the weather is mostly cold with high humidity all year round, the best time to visit the Faroe Islands is from May to September. Late spring and early summer bring longer days, wildflowers, and Atlantic puffins. Warm and humid August sees the largest tourist crowds, so book a room in advance.</string>
    <!-- Fiji -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_fj">Temperatures stay pretty constant through the whole year, with highs resting in the 80s; however, from November to April, you might have to contend with some tropical storms. Peak season occurs between July and September, when the weather is dry and sunny.</string>
    <!-- Finland -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_fi">It depends on what you\'d like to experience: for plenty of snow and winter activities, December to March is the best time. For springtime sun and the revival of nature after the winter, April to May is the period. For long and warm summer days and plenty of events, opt for June, July and August.</string>
    <!-- France -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_fr">The best time to visit France is in the spring (April to June) or fall (September to November) when there are fewer tourists, lower prices, and moderate temperatures. The summer months can be hot, crowded, and expensive.</string>
    <!-- French Guiana -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gf">The best time to visit French Guyana is from mid-August to mid-November, and in particular the months of September and October, which are the least rainy and the sunniest, especially on the eastern part of the country.</string>
    <!-- French Polynesia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pf">French Polynesia is at its best between June and August when the climate is at its driest and the weather is balmy, sitting comfortably in the high 20s to mid 30s Celsius. However, this can be a slightly busier time of year and the months either side of this period can see comfortable temperatures, but lower prices.</string>
    <!-- French Southern Territories -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tf">The growing season in French Southern Territories typically lasts for 6.9 months (210 days), from around October 30 to around May 28, rarely starting before October 7 or after November 20, and rarely ending before May 4 or after June 21.</string>
    <!-- Gabon -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ga">The best time to visit Gabon is during the drier season of May to September, with June, July and August being the driest months, although \'dry\' is relative here – Gabon experiences around 2.5m of rainfall a year.</string>
    <!-- Gambia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gm">There\'s two distinct seasons that will influence when you decide is the best time to visit The Gambia. The dry season runs from October to June and this is when you\'ll see a decrease in humidity. Winter holidays are great if you want to avoid the heat and heavy rainfall of the summer.</string>
    <!-- Georgia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ge">The best time to visit Georgia is May, June or September, especially in the lowlands around Tbilisi, as you\'ll avoid the summer heat and humidity as well as the freezing winter.</string>
    <!-- Germany -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_de">May. Overview of weather in Germany in May: Falling just before the summer crowds converge, May is a great time to travel to Germany. Temperatures begin to warm up and the sun makes more appearances throughout the month. Also, the beginning of October clocks in among the best times to visit Germany. The weather in Germany in October can still be pleasantly warm at times. Other than catching the tail-end of Oktoberfest in Munich, hotels in Germany begin reverting back to low season prices. </string>
    <!-- Ghana -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gh">The best time to visit Ghana is between November - March, when there is little to no rainfall, and every part of the country is easily accessible. Between April and October, the weather in Ghana is rather wet, restricting the ability to travel. Many places might close down for the low-season as well.</string>
    <!-- Gibraltar -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gi">The best time to visit Gibraltar often falls around the season, which occurs during August to September. The winter season in Gibraltar, like in Spain, occurs from the month of December up to March.</string>
    <!-- Greece -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gr">Just about everyone agrees that the best time to visit is Greece is spring and early summer (mid-Apr to mid-June) or autumn (Sept to mid-Oct). This way, you\'ll avoid the summer high season, with its inflated prices, hordes of tourists and high temperatures (heat waves of 100°F/+40C are routine).</string>
    <!-- Greenland -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gl">Summer in Greenland lasts from June through to September and is very unique. The days are long and bright. It is the best time to visit if you want to go hiking and get involved in lots of outdoor activities. It is also the time when you can witness the midnight sun – typical of an Arctic summer.</string>
    <!-- Grenada -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gd">Grenada enjoys a hot, tropical climate all year round, tempered by cooling trade winds, with an average high of 29°C to 30°C. The driest months are typically January to May. From June to December the rain usually falls in brief, very heavy showers.</string>
    <!-- Guadeloupe -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gp">The best time to visit Guadeloupe is from December to May, when the weather remains warm and dry and daily highs rest in the mid-80s. Though pleasant temperatures last year-round, August and September\'s hurricane season can threaten your travel plans.</string>
    <!-- Guam -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gu">The wet season is July through November, with transitional months being June and December. The best time to visit is Jan-May, the dry season.</string>
    <!-- Guatemala -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gt">Guatemala has a pleasant climate that lends itself to year-round visits. The dry season runs from November to April, but even in the wet season the rainfall is generally only for a couple of hours a day in the main visitor regions.</string>
    <!-- Guernsey -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gg">Guernsey is enjoyable at any time of the year, even though the best months to travel are May to September.</string>
    <!-- Guinea -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gn">The best time to visit is November and December, after the rains and before the dusty harmattan winds, though the Fouta Djalon is at its greenest and best during the rainy season. April is very hot everywhere and is not a pleasant month to travel in Guinea.</string>
    <!-- Guinea-Bissau -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gw">Expect year-round warmth and humidity in Guinea-Bissau but avoid the rainy season, when its already poor roads become even worse. Guinea-Bissau\'s tropical climate means it\'s generally hot and humid here, with its rainy season falling between June and October.</string>
    <!-- Guyana -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gy">Guyana\'s climate is equatorial: it is hot but pleasant for most of the year. Temperatures average between 24° to 31° Celsius. There are two wet seasons during May and June, and December and January.</string>
    <!-- Haiti -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ht">The weather is at its best during the dry spell from November through to March and this is generally considered the best time to visit Haiti. Heavy rains descend between April and June, followed by a hurricane season from August to October which has slightly lighter rains.</string>
    <!-- Heard Island and McDonald Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_hm">The best time to go to Heard Island and McDonald Islands is from January until December, in which you have a very cold temperature, but little rainfall. The highest average temperature in Heard Island and McDonald Islands is 4° in March and the lowest is 1° in July.</string>
    <!-- Holy See -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_va">You might consider Tuesday or Thursday as your best bets. Dates around a weekend are a bit busier, and on Wednesday there is (usually) the Papal Audience, meaning even more crowds. That being said, from April - October, you can book a visit to the Vatican Museums on Friday night. And it\'s much less crowded then.</string>
    <!-- Honduras -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_hn">Travel to Honduras is possible year round, but the dry season between December and April is generally considered the best time to go. May and November bring hotter, more humid conditions and afternoon downpours, while the later months of the year carry the threat of hurricanes.</string>
    <!-- Hong Kong -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_hk">There are mild, relatively dry winters, and hot, humid, and wet summers. The best time to visit Hong Kong is from October to early December, when the weather is sunny, cool, and pleasant. Spring is a cloudy season in Hong Kong.</string>
    <!-- Hungary -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_hu">The best times to visit Budapest are from March to May and September through November. These shoulder seasons are when the weather is idyllic and the city isn\'t overcrowded with tourists. However, the climate is always relatively mild, with temperatures rarely exceeding bearable levels.</string>
    <!-- Iceland -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_is">The best time to travel to Iceland for good weather is during the summer; this is the peak of Iceland\'s travel season, so expect crowds – or visit in late spring or early fall, when tourist crowds are thinner. The best time to see the Northern Lights is late fall, when nights are most likely to be dark and clear.</string>
    <!-- India -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_in">The best time to visit India is from October to March. India is large with diverse weather patterns. The Himalayas stop cold winds from reaching most of India so winters remain warm and summers can get very hot. The majority of India is tropical and is affected by three main seasons; summer, winter and monsoon.</string>
    <!-- Indonesia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_id">Generally speaking, the best time of year to visit Indonesia is between May and September when the days are dry and sunny. However, during wet season temperatures remain high and rainfall comes in the form of intense tropical downpours that tend to last for a couple of hours and needn\'t spoil your trip.</string>
    <!-- Côte d\'Ivoire -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ci">Côte d\'Ivoire sees rain at different times of the year. In the north the wet season is June-October. In the south there are two rainy seasons: May-July and October-November. The best time to visit is in the cool, dry period between November-February although in December Harmattan winds reduce visibility.</string>
    <!-- Iran (Islamic Republic of) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ir">Generally the best time to visit Iran is during the spring and autumn. There are ideal temperatures across most of Iran from March until May and then again from late September to early November. Meanwhile, winter is best avoided because temperatures can become very cold.</string>
    <!-- Iraq -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_iq">The best months to visit Iraq are in spring and autumn, away from the sweltering heat and the winter chills. Late May to early September are very hot and dry in Iraq, with temperatures well above 40°C. At this time, your best escape route is the slightly cooler mountains in the north and east.</string>
    <!-- Ireland -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ie">The best time to visit Ireland is in April, May, and June, as well as in September and October. Even though there are never any promises when it comes to Irish weather, spring and autumn tend to be relatively mild and have fewer crowds (and lower prices) than during the peak of summer.</string>
    <!-- Isle of Man -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_im">Autumn is a good time to visit Isle of Man as it avoids the peak summer tourist season, where the island is very popular among visitors whilst still having milder temperatures and longer hours of daylight particularly at the start of September.</string>
    <!-- Israel -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_il">The seasons of spring April - May and between mid of August - October are the best time to visit Israel when temperatures are pleasantly mild throughout the country.</string>
    <!-- Italy -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_it">The best months for traveling in much of Italy are from April to June and mid-September to October: Temperatures are usually comfortable, rural colors are rich, and the crowds aren\'t too intense (except around Easter). From July through early September the country\'s holiday spots teem with visitors.</string>
    <!-- Jamaica -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_jm">The best time to visit Jamaica is November to mid-December. That\'s when the island\'s already beautiful weather (ranging from mid-70s to the high 80s all year-round) is the most pleasant and the hotel and flight deals are the easiest to find.</string>
    <!-- Japan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_jp">Late spring (March to May) and late autumn (September to November) are generally the best times to visit Japan, when there is little rainfall, skies are clear, and temperatures are mild. What\'s more, the delicate cherry blossom of spring and vivid hues of autumn leaves are visually stunning.</string>
    <!-- Jersey -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_je">May through October has the best weather in Jersey. The best time for sunbathers is July and August, but for sightseers and for overall value, look for a trip in May, June and September through early October. Temperatures are in the 60\'s°F by day and 50°F by night, plus it is quieter with tourists.</string>
    <!-- Jordan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_jo">For cooler temperatures in the high teens, the best time to visit Jordan is March-May. Amman reaches a comfortable 32°C between June and September, while nights can drop below freezing from December to February. The beaches of Aqaba and the salty Dead Sea touch 40°C in July.</string>
    <!-- Kazakhstan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_kz">The best time to visit Kazakhstan is between July - August, when the weather is perfect throughout the country. This is the peak season, and the best time for hikers to visit. April - June, and September - October are also a decent time to visit Kazakhstan. The steppes are particularly beautiful during this time.</string>
    <!-- Kenya -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ke">The best wildlife viewing months in Kenya are during the Dry season from late June to October. The wildebeest migration usually reaches the Masai Mara in July and remains until October when they move back to the Serengeti in Tanzania. Wildlife viewing is good year-round, but this can differ for some parks.</string>
    <!-- Kiribati -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ki">The best times of the year to travel to Kiribati is anywhere between April to October. Expect the climate to range at around 30 degree Celsius. Meanwhile, expect regular rainfall and cyclones on the months of November to March.</string>
    <!-- Kuwait -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_kw">The best time to travel to Kuwait is either in the spring (between March and May) or during autumn (September and October). The temperatures are milder and there is little rain and these are the best months for enjoying Kuwait\'s beaches. The winter months are also pleasant times to go to Kuwait.</string>
    <!-- Kyrgyzstan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_kg">June to September is the best time to go to Kyrgyzstan. You can hike, ride horses, stay with traditional families in yurts and cycle around. April, May and October are also OK, but hiking opportunities are less (unless you can handle the snow) and the yurts have already come down from the jailoos.</string>
    <!-- Laos -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_la">The small, landlocked country of Laos is best visited between October and April, when the weather\'s warm and dry throughout. River travel is best between November and January, when high water levels make passage easy along Laos\' main waterway, the Mekong River.</string>
    <!-- Latvia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_lv">The Baltics do live up to their icy reputation in winter - so the best time to visit Latvia is between April and September. Birders will enjoy the spring and autumn migrations, with flocks of ducks, geese and divers, and the autumn foliage is a sight to behold. Don\'t overlook Latvia\'s culture - with waking tours of Riga, delicious black bread, cheese and sweets, and vibrant markets in which to practise your haggling skills.</string>
    <!-- Lebanon -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_lb">While it has four distinct seasons, uniquely for a Middle Eastern country, and so can be visited all year-round, the best time to go to Lebanon is definitely spring. The weather is pleasantly warm and dry, ideal for the coast, the mountains and exploring the country’s many historic sites.</string>
    <!-- Lesotho -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ls">We chose to travel Swaziland, South Africa and Lesotho in June, mainly for the mild winter climate and better wildlife opportunities. June to September is the winter dry season in South Africa, Swaziland and Lesotho.</string>
    <!-- Liberia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_lr">The December to July dry season is the most popular time to visit. During the rains, which usually begin in May or June and peter out in October, there are spectacular storms and good waves for surfers. Liberia is humid most of the year with annual rainfall heavy in Monrovia and along the coast.</string>
    <!-- Libya -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ly">The best time to go to Libya is from January until December, in which you have a pleasant till hot temperature and none till barely rainfall. The highest average temperature in Libya is 35° in july and the lowest is 18° in january.</string>
    <!-- Liechtenstein -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_li">Liechtenstein is ready for visitors any time of the year. If you want high-energy winter sports, Alpine resorts open towards the end of November.</string>
    <!-- Lithuania -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_lt">Best time to visit Lithuania. Although the coast is tempting in summer, the Baltic Sea breeze can drop temps quite dramatically so pack layers to be on the safe side. Short summers and freezing winters set the scene with beach time in the Baltics best enjoyed from June to August.</string>
    <!-- Luxembourg -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_lu">You can visit Luxembourg at any time, but bear in mind that the availability of services in some regions varies with the seasons. May, June and September are usually very pleasant months, as the weather is often at its most benign during late spring and late summer.</string>
    <!-- Macao -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mo">Macau climate from April to October is rainy. May is the rainiest and July to September is the typhoon season. Autumn and winter, especially mid-October to December, are recommended as the best visit times.</string>
    <!-- Macedonia (the former Yugoslav Republic of) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mk">The best time to visit Macedonia is generally between the summer months of June to September, however these are also the busiest months of travel to the country. Its temporal climate means it is fine to visit anytime from April onwards.</string>
    <!-- Madagascar -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mg">Whilst Madagascar holidays can be enjoyed year-round, the principal wet season is from late December through to the month of March; often involving cyclones, it is probably best avoided! The best time to go to Madagascar is therefore between the months of April through to mid-December</string>
    <!-- Malawi -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mw">Malawi has a hot summer rainfall season from November to April so the best time to visit is during the drier winter months - early May to late October. Winter gets chilly high up on the northern Nyika Plateau but down on the shore of Lake Malawi you can expect warm, sunny and dry days - great beach weather!</string>
    <!-- Malaysia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_my">Overall, the best time to visit Malaysia is between the months of December and February, if you\'re planning on visiting the islands on the west side of Malaysia (e.g., Penang and Langkawi), or June through August if you\'re planning to visit Perhentians and Tioman Island, on the country\'s Eastern coast.Jan 24, 2019</string>
    <!-- Maldives -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mv">The Maldives are hot and sunny all year round, with average temperatures of 23ºC-31ºC. The best weather – and the best time to visit the Maldives – is between November and April. The high season falls between December and March. The monsoon runs from May to October, peaking around June.</string>
    <!-- Mali -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ml">The months between November and January, which Malians call the "cold season," is the most comfortable time to visit weather-wise. Northeast alize winds keep average temperatures to a relatively cool 90°F. Visitors coming to Mali during the wettest months from July to September actually won\'t experience very much rain.</string>
    <!-- Malta -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mt">After traditional Easter celebrations it\'s blue skies all the way from March through to October with springtime and autumn the best time to visit Malta outside of the hotter, more crowded, summer months.</string>
    <!-- Marshall Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mh">The busiest month for tourism in the Marshall Islands is November, followed by June and March. Prices for hotels and flights will be most expensive during these months, though you can save if you purchase well in advance. Tourists are unlikely to visit the Marshall Islands in December.</string>
    <!-- Martinique -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mq">Temperatures climb into the mid-80s, and Martinique hotels are often available at discounted rates (when compared to the December to April season). For the best bargain, start looking for a vacation package in winter. The definitive rainy season on the island, summer and fall are when many hotels choose to shut down.</string>
    <!-- Mauritania -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mr">Mauritania is mostly hot and dry with little rain, though the coast is tempered by tradewinds. The winter season of November to March is the best time to visit Mauritania, when it\'s warm but not scorching, though nights can be chilly.</string>
    <!-- Mauritius -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mu">The best time to visit Mauritius is from May to December when the weather is cool, dry and sunny. Expect some of Africa\'s best beaches, fresh seafood and long, sundrenched days on a Mauritius holiday. The island has a classic tropical climate with warm weather year-round.</string>
    <!-- Mayotte -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_yt">Rain is present during all months, but is more and heavier from November to May. August to October is the driest period and temperatures are fine as well, making this the best time to travel to Mayotte. Hurricanes are possible from December to February, so it is best to avoid this time.</string>
    <!-- Mexico -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mx">The best time to visit Mexico is during the dry season between December and April, when there is virtually no rain. The coolest months are between December and February, although temperatures can still reach averages of 28℃ during the dry season. The wet season begins in the south in May and lasts until October.</string>
    <!-- Micronesia (Federated States of) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_fm">The best time to go to Micronesia is from January until March and October, in which you have a warm temperature and much rainfall. The highest average temperature in Micronesia is 32° in April and the lowest is 31° in January.</string>
    <!-- Moldova (Republic of) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_md">The best time to visit Moldova for walking with wildflowers or bird watching is May to June but remember a raincoat as heavy showers can be frequent. Independence Day at the end of August is also worth experiencing, and October finds the countryside alive with colour but, again, don\'t forget your mac and brolly.</string>
    <!-- Monaco -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mc">The best time to visit Monaco is in the spring or fall. April and October are both ideal months for a vacation: the weather is balmy and the room rates are reduced.</string>
    <!-- Mongolia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mn">The best time to visit Mongolia is during July and August, the peak summer months when the weather is pleasant and warm, around 25 degrees and the landscape is green and lush.</string>
    <!-- Montenegro -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_me">The nicest seasons to visit Montenegro are spring and autumn: either between late March, by which time even in the high mountain regions the ‘ice days’ should have passed, and the end of June; or in September and October after the summer vacationers have dispersed, when the deciduous trees will be turning coppery but the sea will still be warm enough for bathing. July and August are the best months only for those who like family fun and crowds. As a local hotelier put it, speaking of the ‘Montenegrin Riviera’, while the under-30s will love the nightlife and buzz of the town beaches in July and August, those seeking a quieter ambience may prefer to visit the coast during the bridge months – April/May/June or September/October. In the mountains, July and August are guaranteed to be temperate.</string>
    <!-- Montserrat -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ms">Many believe the months between February and May are the most ideal to visit Montserrat, when the island\'s climate is at its driest and the risk of hurricanes is lowest.</string>
    <!-- Morocco -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ma">The country is at its most beautiful in spring (mid-March to May) when the landscape is green and lush, making for spectacular mountain hiking. Morocco is also lovely in Autumn (September to October) when temperatures are very pleasant.</string>
    <!-- Mozambique -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mz">The May to November winter season is when to go to Mozambique for cooler temperatures and the least chance of rain; December to April is the wet summer season although it generally rains in brief but vigorous downpours after which the sun comes out again.</string>
    <!-- Myanmar -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mm">From October onwards the rains subside; the best time to visit most of Myanmar is from November to February, when temperatures are relatively manageable. From March to May, the country becomes very hot, particularly the dry zone of the central plains where Bagan and Mandalay often see temperatures in excess of 40°C.</string>
    <!-- Namibia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_na">Between December and March, some days will be humid and rain may follow, often in localized, afternoon thunderstorms. Wildlife viewing in all parks, but especially in Etosha, is best in the Dry season from June to October. In the Wet season, animals move away from the waterholes and scatter around the park.</string>
    <!-- Nauru -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_nr">The best time to visit Nauru is during the island\'s dry season, which begins in March and ends in October. These are also the months when the northeast trade winds are most effective at cooling off the heat on this island whose average humidity is 80 percent and the weather is most pleasant.</string>
    <!-- Nepal -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_np">As the monsoon dissipates in September, Nepal welcomes beautiful clear skies, fresh air and incredible views. October and November are two of the best months to visit as dry days make trekking easier and offer good visibility. The verdant landscapes following the rains are ideal for photographers.</string>
    <!-- Netherlands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_nl">The best time weather wise is from mid April to mid October. July and August are the peak months for visitors. The weather overall is never severely cold or hot as the temperatures are influenced by the North Sea (the Netherlands has a maritime climate). Most rain falls in the winter and it can feel damp and chilly.</string>
    <!-- New Caledonia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_nc">It is best to visit New Caledonia from September to November when it is warm and sunny with temperatures from 26&#8211;30°C. Temperatures begin to rise and this is the least rainy months of the year. This is the peak season of the year when tourists go on holidays with higher hotel prices.</string>
    <!-- New Zealand -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_nz">New Zealand truly does come into its own in the summer, as an outdoor lover\'s paradise. Particularly between the months of December to February you\'ll see people at the beach, hiking in the forest or biking on our cycling trails. It\'s a popular time of year for getting outdoors in nature, and experiencing life at a slower pace.</string>
    <!-- Nicaragua -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ni">Visiting Nicaragua in November - April. Nicaragua\'s dry season begins in November, when the majority of places enjoy dry, sunny days and mild temperatures. This makes it the ideal time for exploring the colonial cities, beaches, volcanoes and nature reserves the country is so famous for.</string>
    <!-- Niger -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ne">If visiting the south and west of the country, there is a slightly increased wet season between June and September.</string>
    <!-- Nigeria -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ng">Nigeria is consistently hot all year round with very little change in temperature, and in the south there is a constant uncomfortable humidity. Temperatures are highest from February to April in the south and from March to June in the north, and lowest from October to January over most of the country.</string>
    <!-- Niue -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_nu">The weather is hotter and the risk of cyclones is greater during the wetter of Niue\'s two major seasons, which begins in November and lasts until April.</string>
    <!-- Norfolk Island -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_nf">The best time to visit Norfolk Island runs from October to March, when the rains are less heavy, the sunshine more frequent and the temperature pleasant. The warmest months, where you can also swim in the sea, are January, February and March.</string>
    <!-- Korea (Democratic People\'s Republic of) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_kp">The best time to visit North Korea is in spring or autumn, when days are relatively mild and clear; as generally the country experiences cool and cold sunny winters, and warm, humid summers, when most of the rainfall occurs.</string>
    <!-- Northern Mariana Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mp">The dry season months from December to June are the most ideal time to come to the Northern Mariana Islands. Those wishing to avoid crowds should stay away during Japanese national holidays, many of which fall during the islands\' dry season.</string>
    <!-- Norway -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_no">The best time to visit Norway depends on what you want to do. Jun-Aug promise long days and the fabled midnight sun ideal for hiking, cycling or cruising – but no guarantee of heat, even if it won\'t be cold! May and Sep offer mild temperatures, fewer crowds and gorgeous natural colours.</string>
    <!-- Oman -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_om">Oman has a reliably warm climate and, as long as you avoid the scorching summer months between June and August, can be visited any time. The weather is at its most pleasant from October through to April, when temperatures are warm but cooler than the sweltering summer months and turtles can be seen at Ras al Jinz.</string>
    <!-- Pakistan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pk">May - October is generally the best season to visit, as the weather is rather dry and warm throughout the country.</string>
    <!-- Palau -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pw">Palau is an outstanding destination year round. The best diving in Palau is between November and April. These months have the greatest number of pelagics, and has incredible visibility.</string>
    <!-- Palestine, State of -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ps">The best time to visit Palestine, especially if hiking, is outside the hottest months, June-Sep. So when autumn leaves start turning at home, turn your thoughts to wild and wonderful walking in Palestine. Spring is perfect, as cyclamen, iris and anemones are in bloom.</string>
    <!-- Panama -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pa">Humidity is always high in Panama, and rainfall varies noticeably between the Pacific and Caribbean sides of the country, with some areas in the Caribbean receiving almost twice the yearly rainfall of Panama City. The best time to visit Panama is during the summer dry season from mid-December to mid-April.</string>
    <!-- Papua New Guinea -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pg">The drier months of May through to October is generally the most pleasant time to visit. It\'s also when many of the festivals are held. In most parts of PNG, diving is good year-round; Milne Bay however, has the best visibility from September to January and from April to June.</string>
    <!-- Paraguay -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_py">Paraguay\'s peak tourist season is from April to September. During this period, there are plenty of festivals and comfortable weather. If you\'re looking for cooler temperatures during your vacation to Paraguay, plan on visiting from May till August, also known as the winter season.</string>
    <!-- Peru -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pe">The winter (May – September) is the driest season and therefore the best time of year to travel, especially if you\'re planning to visit Cusco or trek to Machu Picchu. The summer (December – March) is warmer of course, but is also the wettest season, with frequent heavy showers.</string>
    <!-- Philippines -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ph">The Philippines are most popular during the dry season, between November and April. At this time the country is fully accessible, including its many beautiful islands and more remote areas. Temperatures are high during March and April, so it\'s best to travel during the cooler months of December to February.</string>
    <!-- Pitcairn -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pn">The best time to go to Pitcairn Islands is in February and March and May until December, in which you have a pleasant or warm temperature and little till mediocre rainfall. The highest average temperature in Pitcairn Islands is 28° in February and the lowest is 21° in September.</string>
    <!-- Poland -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pl">If you’re wondering when is the best time to visit Poland then it all depends on whether you’re looking for animal or Nordic ski tracks in the snow or hoping to make the most of the beautiful beaches along the Baltic coastline. Spring and autumn are certainly the best time to visit Poland for hiking and cycling with the High Tatras offering plenty of things to do for lovers of the great outdoors.</string>
    <!-- Portugal -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pt">The best time to visit Portugal is in spring (March-May), when the country is in bloom and waking after the winter. You could also go in fall (between September and October) when the sun is still shining, the weather is warm, and many of the crowds have dispersed.</string>
    <!-- Puerto Rico -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pr">The best time to visit Puerto Rico is from mid-April to June, right after the busy winter season and just before the rainy summer. Spring weather is also very pleasant, barely escaping the mid-80s on most days.</string>
    <!-- Qatar -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_qa">The best months to visit Qatar are November early April. Such climatic conditions allow sightseeing and outdoor activities across the country and these are considered as peak-tourist season in Qatar. The summer months (June to September) are very hot with minimum rainfall, so these are best avoided.</string>
    <!-- Republic of Kosovo -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_xk">Sometimes people forget that Kosovo is located in southern Europe, so temperatures can get really hot in summer, although the average in July and August is the high 20s centigrade. Similarly it snows in winter, so the best times to visit Kosovo are April to September.</string>
    <!-- Réunion -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_re">Réunion has a hot sub-tropical climate with sea temperatures that rarely drop below 23°C. The dry season is May to October, with temperatures 20&#8211;25°C. November to March is more humid, with most rain and occasional cyclones in January and February.</string>
    <!-- Romania -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ro">However, referring strictly to the temperatures here, the best time to visit Romania would be mid-May through mid-September. Visiting Romania during late spring or early fall will provide you with the best possible weather, as you will be able to enjoy lots of sunshine, as well as comfortable temperatures.</string>
    <!-- Russian Federation -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ru">The wettest months are October and November. The best time to visit St. Petersburg is late spring and early June. It\'s the season when the weather is the most inviting for long hours of walks in the city. Plus, Saint Petersburg is famous for its white nights, which are best to see in May and June.</string>
    <!-- Rwanda -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_rw">Then from June to mid-September is the long dry season; this is generally the best time to visit if you have the choice. October to November is a shorter rainy season and it\'s followed by a short dry season from December to February. During both of Rwanda\'s dry seasons, there is often light cloud cover.</string>
    <!-- Saint Barthélemy -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_bl">November through June is the best time to visit St. Bart\'s. From December through April, the sun is especially scorching. December is considered peak season and requires bookings six months in advance. Clouds and showers sometimes interrupt the warm weather, especially during the fall.</string>
    <!-- Saint Helena, Ascension and Tristan da Cunha -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sh">The main tourist season on St Helena is from November to March, when it is summer in the southern hemisphere and the days are predominantly sunny and hot. You can expect some rainfall, especially out of Jamestown in March, but rarely does it last long at this time of year.</string>
    <!-- Saint Kitts and Nevis -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_kn">The best time to visit St. Kitts and Nevis is in May and June, when hotels lower their rates to lure in travelers and the winter crowds thin out. But the peak season – December to April – does host Carnival, a party that might be worth weaving through the droves of tourists.</string>
    <!-- Saint Lucia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_lc">High season in Saint Lucia is from mid-December to mid-April.Rainy season is officially from June-November, but September and October are when the hurricanes are most likely to hit.</string>
    <!-- Saint Martin (French part) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_mf">The best time to visit St. Martin and St. Maarten is May and June or between November and mid-December. These select weeks are times when hotels advertise their best rates. The island\'s weather is pleasant year-round, but these are times when rain showers are less likely.</string>
    <!-- Saint Pierre and Miquelon -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_pm">Late summer and early autumn are a bit more sunny and warm, July, August and September are the best months to visit these islands, that are last piece of the vast empire that France had in North America in the seventeenth and eighteenth century.</string>
    <!-- Saint Vincent and the Grenadines -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_vc">The best time to visit St. Vincent and The Grenadines is from May to June and in November. During these shoulder months, hotels drop their rates to attract travelers. The peak season—December through April—lures the most European visitors with its warm Caribbean temperatures.</string>
    <!-- Samoa -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ws">Best time to visit Samoa, weather-wise: July to September enjoys pleasant temperatures with dry weather and low levels of humidity. Cheapest time to visit Samoa: Prices are lowest during February and March due to heavy rainfall and the possibility of typhoons.</string>
    <!-- San Marino -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sm">Probably the best time to visit San Marino is from April to June or from mid-September to the end of October. During these months, the temperature is at its most pleasant. July, August and the first half of September can be hot, though breezes that come up from the ocean generally keep things cool.</string>
    <!-- Sao Tome and Principe -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_st">Two beautiful islands deserve two dry seasons. The first is Dec-Feb and the second is from June to September. The best time to go to São Tomé and Príncipe for bird watching – and there are a lot to watch – is Oct-March. Feb-May is when the heavens can open, but then paradise does need watering from time to time.</string>
    <!-- Saudi Arabia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sa">The best time to visit Saudi Arabia is during winter between the months of late October and early March. However, Asir Mountains, located in the south-western part of Saudi Arabia, are impregnable in winters due to excessive fog, and should be visited either before November or after February.</string>
    <!-- Senegal -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sn">The best time of year to travel to Senegal is between November and May, during the dry season. Throughout this period, the temperature tends to be around 25 degrees Celsius. However, between June and October, precipitation is very frequent and the temperatures sometimes 30 degrees Celsius or above.</string>
    <!-- Serbia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_rs">The best time to visit Serbia for good weather is during the summer months but, beyond the massive EXIT Festival in early July (which draws revellers from across Europe), Serbia doesn\'t see huge influxes of visitors, making it an ideal spot to avoid the crowds just about year-round.</string>
    <!-- Seychelles -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sc">The best times to visit Seychelles are April, May, October and November. These months represent the transition times between the hot and humid northwest trade winds (from November through March) and the cooler southeast trade winds that define April through October.</string>
    <!-- Sierra Leone -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sl">The best time to go to Sierra Leone is in the dry season, which runs from October to May. January and February tend to be the hottest months. Birders will find December or January most rewarding. Travel is possible in June and late September although there will be heavy down pours and rural roads can become very muddy.</string>
    <!-- Singapore -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sg">Overall, the best time to go to Singapore is between February and April. Although Singapore is—for the most part—a year-round destination, the months of February to April fall within Singapore\'s dry season and experience (a least a tad) less rainfall than other times of the year.</string>
    <!-- Sint Maarten (Dutch part) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sx">The best time to visit St. Martin and St. Maarten is May and June or between November and mid-December. These select weeks are times when hotels advertise their best rates. The island\'s weather is pleasant year-round, but these are times when rain showers are less likely.</string>
    <!-- Slovakia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sk">Bratislava belongs to warmest and driest places in SLovakia. End of March, April, May, September and October temperatures are mild. I would recommend to anyone to visit Bratislava these months: you will not be sweating, and you can enjoy just normal temperature.</string>
    <!-- Slovenia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_si">The best time to visit Slovenia is different for everyone. The alpine northwest sees abundant snow Dec-March, while warm, dry conditions May-Sep are ideal for climbing, hiking, cycling and adventure sports. Snow melt makes white water rafting a great option by late May.</string>
    <!-- Solomon Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sb">June and July are also part of the peak tourist season. Prices for the main tourist resorts tend to fall during the rainy seasons. However, tourists do need to contend with high humidity and heavy storms if traveling during the months of February, March, April, September, and October.</string>
    <!-- Somalia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_so">The best time to visit the country is early during the second winter dry season, Hagaa, in the months of January and February. At this time, the humidity of the rainy season has subsided but the temperatures are also not as high as those experienced during the first dry season, Jilal.</string>
    <!-- South Africa -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_za">South Africa is a year-round destination due to its varying regional climates and wildlife opportunities. The Cape has beautiful hot, dry weather in its summer months between November and February, while the best time to visit for whale watching is between July and November.</string>
    <!-- South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gs">Like Antarctica, South Georgia can only be visited during the 5-month summer window, running from late October to March. But deciding when the best time to visit South Georgia Island is during this period really comes down to what you want to experience during your Antarctica cruise adventure.</string>
    <!-- Korea (Republic of) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_kr">South Korea has four distinct seasons. The summer period from June to August sees hot and humid weather whereas winter, from December to February, is icy cold and dry. Autumn and spring are thought to be the best times to visit as they offer warm, sunny days with clear blue skies.</string>
    <!-- South Sudan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ss">The best time to visit South Sudan is in bone-dry December, January or February, when temperatures in Juba city can sit anywhere between 20 and 37°C. The higher in altitude you go, the cooler it gets; remember to pack layers if you\'re staying in the Imatong Hills.</string>
    <!-- Spain -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_es">The best time to visit Spain is either in late spring or early autumn - especially if you\'re going to Andalucia or the Mediterranean coastal areas. Northern Spain is at its peak in the summer months (July and August), and central Spain is best visited in October or May.</string>
    <!-- Sri Lanka -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_lk">In a nutshell, the best time to visit the west and south coasts and hill country is from December to March, while the best weather on the east coast is from April/May to September.</string>
    <!-- Sudan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sd">The best time to visit Sudan is when it deigns to cool just a tad, the lowest temperatures being in Jan, averaging 30°C. However, temperatures can halve at night during Dec-Feb, making travel a lot more bearable.</string>
    <!-- Suriname -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sr">In most respects, however, the best time to visit Suriname is during the relatively dry months of February to March and August to November, and the worst time is during the wettest months of May to August, when the interior in particular is prone to flooding and the already limited road network becomes even more so.</string>
    <!-- Svalbard and Jan Mayen -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sj">Weather stations report very large amounts of snow likely to be deepest around June, especially close to early June. The best time to ski (if at all) in Svalbard and Jan Mayen is often around June 4th when fresh powder is deepest.</string>
    <!-- Swaziland -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sz">The best time to visit Swaziland is during the dry winter months (April to September) which are warm in the day, but cold at night. The summer months (October to March) are hot, with heavy rains.</string>
    <!-- Sweden -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_se">For warm weather and sunshine, the best time to visit Sweden is May to September. If you want snow, aim to go between late November and March. You can visit the country all year round, but you\'ll need to wrap up during winter. – To see the midnight sun, visit in the height of summer (June and July).</string>
    <!-- Switzerland -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ch">The best time to visit Switzerland is during the shoulder seasons, between April and June, and September to October, when the weather is at best, and there aren\'t too many tourists.</string>
    <!-- Syrian Arab Republic -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_sy">Syria experiences typical Mediterranean type climate with hot, dry summers and cold, wet winters. The best time to visit the country is thus between these two seasons, namely during spring and autumn.</string>
    <!-- Taiwan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tw">Spring in Taiwan runs from March to May and temperatures are usually a nice and comfortable 20&#8211;25°C. It\'s a great time to visit and many people come to see the cherry and plum blossoms. Summer in Taiwan is both hot and humid. Winters in Taiwan are pretty mild.</string>
    <!-- Tajikistan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tj">The best time to visit Tajikistan is from June to mid-September. If you go to Tajikistan, you should definitely go to the mountains either – Fann or Pamir Mountains. Tajikistan has a continental climate which means summers are hot and winters are cold.</string>
    <!-- Tanzania, United Republic of -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tz">The best wildlife viewing months in Tanzania are during the Dry season from late June to October. The best chance of seeing the wildebeest migration in the Serengeti is during June and July and the time to see the wildebeest calving is late January to February.</string>
    <!-- Thailand -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_th">Although the climate varies throughout Thailand, you can visit all year round. The best time to travel is during the cool and dry season between November and early April. In the south, the climate differs between the eastern and western coasts.</string>
    <!-- Timor-Leste -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tl">With temperature average from 22ºC to 31ºC, East Timor has a tropical monsoon climate and best time to visit this paradisiacal island is from April to July, that\'s when you get the best weather.</string>
    <!-- Togo -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tg">Rains fall May-October although, in the south, there is a reprise mid-July and mid-September. Fazao-Malfakassa National Park is only open Nov-April. Togo is at its most torrid during March and April, making November to February the best time to visit.</string>
    <!-- Tokelau -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tk">The best time to go to Tokelau is from april until november, in which you have a warm or hot temperature and mediocre till much rainfall. The highest average temperature in Tokelau is 33° in july and the lowest is 31° in august.</string>
    <!-- Tonga -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_to">The best time to visit Tonga is between May and October during the country\'s dry season. The wet season is from November to April, with December and January the wettest months.</string>
    <!-- Trinidad and Tobago -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tt">The best time to visit Trinidad and Tobago is from January to May when the skies stay clear. Although the islands aren\'t on the hurricane belt, afternoon rain showers are daily occurrences from June to December. Hotels lower their rates to account for rainy weather during this wet season.</string>
    <!-- Tunisia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tn">Ideal times to visit are in the springtime, particularly from April to June, when the fields in the north are a picture of blooming poppies and the apricot season is at its height, and again in September and October when the edge comes off the summer heat and the first dates are harvested.</string>
    <!-- Turkey -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tr">Istanbul and European Turkey experience hot summers and cold winters with snow being a common feature. Spring and autumn, from April to May and from September to mid November respectively, are the ideal times to visit Istanbul and the inland regions when temperatures are pleasant and the skies are clear.</string>
    <!-- Turkmenistan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tm">The best time to visit Turkmenistan is from mid March to end of May and then again from mid September to November, when you can expect daytime temperatures of between 23&#8211;35°C. Winter months can be extremely cold and by contrast, July and August are boiling hot, particularly in the desert regions.</string>
    <!-- Turks and Caicos Islands -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tc">The best time to visit Turks and Caicos is April and May, a sweet spot featuring lower prices and fewer crowds. The weather is pleasant year-round with average highs that hover in the 80s, but these islands do experience a rainy season, and the threat of hurricanes lingers from June to November.</string>
    <!-- Tuvalu -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_tv">The best time to travel to Tuvalu is from mid-May to late October, since it is the (relatively) least rainy period, and out of the cyclone season. However, as sometimes there have been cyclones outside of the canonical period, if you want to be on the safe side, you can choose the period from July to mid-October.</string>
    <!-- Uganda -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ug">The best wildlife viewing months in Uganda are during the Dry seasons from June to August and December to February. Primate walks in the forest are a big part of any safari in Uganda. The habitat of rainforests is, by default, very wet, and one can\'t avoid rain completely.</string>
    <!-- Ukraine -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ua">Sunny Days and Pleasant Weather from June to September. If you are planning a trip to Ukraine, consider the summer months which start from June and continue till September. Beginning of the off season from October. Winter months from November to January.</string>
    <!-- United Arab Emirates -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ae">The best time to visit Dubai and Abu Dhabi is during the months of October to April, as during the summer the weather is quite hot with high humidity levels. There is no rainy season, which makes weather in the winter very pleasant.</string>
    <!-- United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_gb">The United Kingdom can be visited at any time of year, as its climate is relatively temperate and, in general, doesn\'t experience extremes during either summer or winter. Overall, spring (late March to early June) and autumn (September to November) are the best times to visit, when it\'s usually warm and dry.</string>
    <!-- United States of America -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_us">Winter is dry and warm, becoming colder further north, while summer is ideal for beach relaxation or hiking in national parks, although it can be very hot and humid. Spring and autumn are the best times to travel, with pleasant temperatures throughout. Hurricanes can occur in the southeast during August and September.</string>
    <!-- Uruguay -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_uy">The best time to visit Uruguay is October through March, when the sun shines and temperatures are mild. Punta del Este overflows with tourists from Argentina in summer; if you\'re seeking a more relaxed time to visit the beaches of the coast, consider going between October and December.</string>
    <!-- Uzbekistan -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_uz">Uzbekistan is best visited during spring and autumn (April to May, and September to early November). During these periods, it\'s typically warm and dry, and you can enjoy the heat of this desert region without it being uncomfortably hot, as it can be during the summer months.</string>
    <!-- Vanuatu -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_vu">Thanks to Vanuatu\'s beautiful tropical climate, the weather is generally good all year round, however conditions are at their best from April to October when temperatures are a comfortable 18°C to 28°C. November to March sees the arrival of the wet season and although showers are generally brief and do not impact most tours and activities, they can also make conditions much warmer and more humid. Year-round water temperatures sit at a mild 22°C to 28°C, so no matter when you visit swimming is always enjoyable.</string>
    <!-- Venezuela (Bolivarian Republic of) -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ve">Venezuela\'s climate is tropical, with wet and dry seasons rather than hot and cold and average temperatures affected largely by altitude. The wet season runs between May and October, when sunny days give way to afternoon downpours.</string>
    <!-- Viet Nam -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_vn">The best time to visit Vietnam is spring (February to April) and autumn (August to October). The temperatures are more moderate and rainfall is lighter. In spring, March and April have the lowest rainfall across all destinations and temperatures are pleasant, though still cool in the far north.</string>
    <!-- Wallis and Futuna -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_wf">The best time to go to Wallis and Futuna is from May until September, in which you have a warm temperature and mediocre rainfall. The highest average temperature in Wallis and Futuna is 32° in january and the lowest is 30° in august.</string>
    <!-- Western Sahara -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_eh">The best time to go to Western Sahara is from May until October, in which you have a pleasant till hot temperature and barely rainfall. The highest average temperature in Western Sahara is 34° in August and the lowest is 23° in January.</string>
    <!-- Yemen -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_ye">In the north and eastern areas you will find a desert climate, very hot and dry. The best times to visit the country are during April/May and September/October, thus avoiding the hot weather in summer and the cold nights of December.</string>
    <!-- Zambia -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_zm">The dry season runs from May to October and is when to go to Zambia for the best game viewing along with pleasantly mild daytime temperatures (although September and October get extremely hot).The rainy season (December to April) is commonly called the "Green Season" as the bush is beautifully thick and green.</string>
    <!-- Zimbabwe -->
    <string name="when_to_travel_to_zw">With mild temperatures, virtually no rain and a low malaria risk, the dry May to October winter season is generally seen as the best time to visit Zimbabwe for game-viewing, although note that September and October are extremely hot and dry months.</string>
</resources>